hyfy.io 2017-05-22

# Privacy — HYFY Screen Recorder

**YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS**

 **Introduction**

Kickdrum Technology Group, LLC (“Kickdrum” or “we” or “us”) has created this Privacy Policy in order to disclose its use of consumer data collected about you. This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 1, 2015. Any questions regarding this policy should be directed by email to support@hyfy.io or https://www.hyfy.io/. You may also contact Kickdrum at 6504 Marblewood Drive, Austin, Texas 78731. The following discloses Kickdrum’s information gathering and dissemination practices for its social networking applications and website.

 **Information Collected and Received**

Kickdrum may collect or receive information about each person who registers with the Kickdrum website and/or applications including, but not limited to, user name, password, first and last name, email address, street address, gender, occupation, and interests. Kickdrum also collects information on the pages you access and other information you may volunteer, such as survey information. Kickdrum may also collect user location information, as further described in the “Global Positioning System” paragraph below.

 **Uses of Information**

WE WILL NEVER SELL YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS, OR ANY OTHER PERSONAL INFORMATION, TO ANY THIRD PARTY WITHOUT YOUR PERMISSION. EVER.

Except as described in this section, we will not disclose your personal information to any third party without notifying you of our intent to share the information and giving you an opportunity to prevent your information from being shared. From time to time, we may partner with companies based on the interests of our users. These partner companies will never see your email address or any other information that could identify you or be used to contact you directly. Any exceptions to this policy of sharing your name, address or email address with a partner company will be done only with your permission. Kickdrum reserves the right to disclose information when required by law. We occasionally use other companies to perform services necessary to our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information. By contractual agreement, those companies must treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, we will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies. Kickdrum may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with Kickdrum’s server and to administer Kickdrum’s web site. Your IP address may also be used to help identify you and your online profile and to gather broad demographic information. The Kickdrum site registration form requires users to give Kickdrum contact information (such as your name and email address) and demographic information (such as your zip code, age, or income level). Kickdrum uses your contact information from the registration form to send you information about Kickdrum and promotional material from some of Kickdrum’s partners. Your contact information may also be used to contact you when necessary. Kickdrum may use demographic and/or profile data to tailor the your experience on the Kickdrum website and/or applications, show you content that Kickdrum thinks you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. The demographic and profile data will be shared with third parties ONLY on an aggregate basis. Furthermore, Kickdrum shall have the right to retain records of all data pertaining to use of the website and applications including, but not limited to, usage, activity logs, and click-throughs. Kickdrum may disclose such data to third parties provided it is grouped with other Kickdrum users’ data and is presented in an aggregate form. For further clarification, Kickdrum owns and shall continue to own all right, title and interest in and to all aggregate and statistical information, benchmarking, comparison, and other analytics or analyses created or developed by Kickdrum from performance and usage data generated through your use of the products or services (collectively, “Aggregate Data”). Aggregate Data is de-identified so that you cannot be identified as the source within the Aggregate Data. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, statements made by our users.

 **Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18, you should use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian and should not submit any personal information to us. If we discover that a person under the age of 13 has provided us with any personal information, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete such person's personal information from all Kickdrum systems.

 **Global Positioning System**

Global Positioning System (GPS) tracking technology may need to be enabled in Kickdrum products and services in order to determine the location (latitude and longitude) of users of the Kickdrum products and services. This information is transmitted to Kickdrum, Kickdrum’s users, and temporarily stored by Kickdrum. Kickdrum does not provide this information to any other third party. This information is used in conjunction with Kickdrum’s applications.

 **Security**

Kickdrum uses industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged between Kickdrum and other companies to help ensure its security. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under Kickdrum’s control. Kickdrum’s servers are backed up regularly and protected by security systems.

 **Cookies**

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. The Kickdrum site uses cookies to keep track of your session, shopping cart, and advertising delivery. Kickdrum may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password. Kickdrum may use an outside ad company to display ads on the Kickdrum site. These ads may also contain cookies. While Kickdrum uses cookies in other parts of its web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by Kickdrum’s ad company and Kickdrum does not have access to this information. We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use on our sites and software. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our users to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities. We may allow third parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site and/or software. Kickdrum and these companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with these advertisements and connect to the Kickdrum properties and/or software. Our properties do not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows Kickdrum and these companies to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

 **Links**

Kickdrum may create links to other web sites. Kickdrum will make a reasonable effort to link only to sites that meet similar standards for maintaining each individual's right to privacy. However, many other sites that are not associated or authorized by Kickdrum may have links leading to our site. Kickdrum cannot control these links and Kickdrum is not responsible for any content appearing on these sites.

 **Amendments**

Kickdrum may amend this policy at any time. If Kickdrum is going to use personally identifiable information collected through the Kickdrum site in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, Kickdrum will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on the Kickdrum site for thirty (30) days prior to such use. This Privacy Policy may not be otherwise amended except in a writing that specifically refers to this Privacy Policy and is physically signed by both parties.

 **Successors and Assigns**

This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of successors and assigns of Kickdrum.

 **Contacts**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact support@hyfy.io. Upon request, Kickdrum will provide you with access to information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that Kickdrum collects and maintains about you. This site gives you the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: (i) email: support@hyfy.io; or (ii) visit https://www.hyfy.io/.

 **Opt-Out**

The Kickdrum site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Kickdrum. To opt-out of receiving our communications, you can (i) send email to support@hyfy.io; or (ii) send postal mail to: Kickdrum Technology Group, LLC, 6504 Marblewood Drive, Austin, Texas 78731.
